{
    "id": "b7beadc0ba6e4971973f036ea56eff34",
    "title": "Other and another",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "877c9e9543cf45e6ac09395fc2a72888",
            "title": "Other And Another",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She has bought ………………. car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "an other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They looked into each ………………… eyes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "others",
                        "other's",
                        "another's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could I have ………………. cup of coffee, please?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "an other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We all should love one ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "an other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ……………… people haven’t arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "an other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Many ……………….. feel the same.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I’ve met James, but I haven’t met the ………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is staying here for ………………. few weeks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why don’t you think about …………………?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where are the …………….. photos?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}